Preliminary Inventory of the United States Army Air Forces, Air Matériel Command T-2, Air Documents Division Translation Section translations
Hoover Institution Archives
- Box 26
  - Doetsch: "Profilmessungen im 5 m x 7 m windkanal der DVL,", 27 February 1937 (Box-folder 26: 8)
  - Slevogt: "Propagation of ultrashort waves along a dielectric conductor,", January 1942 (Box-folder 26: 9)
  - Zisler & Zintl: "Rudder unit as antenna for radio and blind landing device,", 1 March 1943 (Box-folder 26: 10)
  - Scherbarth: "Three and six component measurements on a model of the Me 262,", October 1942 (Box-folder 26: 11)
  - Philips: "Universal electronic measuring instrument,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 26: 12)
  - Dieckmann: "Use of metal vehicles as antennas,", November 1935 (Box-folder 26: 13)
  - Roeber & Scholkemeier: "Wind tunnel tests on a swept-back wing in the large French wind tunel at Chalais-Meudon,", November 1945 (Box-folder 26: 14)
- Box 27
  - Gerecke: "3-component measurements on a rectangular airfoil profile NACA 23012-64 with fore and back split flaps of different position along the chord,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 27: 1)
  - Weber: "3-component tests on several drop-grenades in the wind tunnel at subsonic velocities,", 1945 (Box-folder 27: 2)
  - Thiel: "The 6th report on gliders" - "Most favorable glider flight-path design: Oscillation free gliding paths,", 10 June 1942 (Box-folder 27: 3)
  - Schmidt: "Calculation of the flow pattern around a given airplane fuselage,", June 1945 (Box-folder 27: 4)
  - Scholz: "Calculation of trajectory. Detail analysis of flight path of A-4 rocket,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 27: 5)
  - Wagner: "Calculations on the possibliity of attaining high Mach numbers in wind tunnel tests,", 22 March 1942 (Box-folder 27: 6)
  - Schlaefke: "Comparison of diagrams with linear and quadratic damping,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 27: 7)
  - Borbely: "Concerning the airforces which act on a two dimensional oscillating airfoil moving at supersonic speed,", August 1942 (Box-folder 27: 8)
  - Schubert: "Contribution to the theory of aircraft control,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 27: 9)
  - De Vries: "The Dornier phaste-testing device for oscillation tests,", 1944 (Box-folder 27: 10)
  - Schlippe & Dietrich: "Flutter of a wheel with pneumatic tire,", 1943 (Box-folder 27: 11)
  - "Junkers wing construction for a fighter,", October 1945 (Box-folder 27: 12)
  - Drescher: "Measurements on a wing with harmonically moved aileron in plane flow,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 27: 13)
  - Pfeiffer, Koenig & Meyer: "Methods of characteristics in stationary two-dimensional gas flows with axial symmetry,", circa 1940 (Box-folder 27: 14)
  - Wehmer: "Noise-proofing of aircraft cabins,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 27: 15)
  - Wockner & Augsburg: "Principles of design of suction airships and preliminary flight operations,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 27: 16)
  - Weyde: "Projected turbojet fighter with two HeS oil turbojet engines,", November 1944 (Box-folder 27: 17)
  - Loeffler: "Study of plasticizers,", 1941 (Box-folder 27: 18)
  - Multhopp: "A swept-back wing at high speeds,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 27: 19)
  - Herlizius: "Test flight of jet propelled fighter Me 262 to observe speed up to 1000 KM,", 26 June 1944 (Box-folder 27: 20)
  - Weber - Kehl: "Tests on Hs 117 device at subsonic speeds,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 27: 21)
  - "Unpublished research on Africa - completed and in progress,", April 1953 (Box-folder 27: 22)
  - "Unpublished research on American Republics (excluding the United States) - completed and in progress,", April 1953 (Box-folder 27: 23)
  - "Unpublished research on British Commonwealth - completed and in progress,", April 1953 (Box-folder 27: 24)
  - "Unpublished research on China - completed and in progress,", April 1953 (Box-folder 27: 25)
  - "Unpublished research on Eastern Europe - completed and in progress,", April 1953 (Box-folder 27: 26)
  - "Unpublished research on Far East and Asia general and regional - completed and in progress,", April 1953 (Box-folder 27: 27)
  - "Unpublished research on International Affairs - economic, social, organizational and informational - completed and in progress,", April 1953 (Box-folder 27: 28)
  - "Unpublished research on Japan - completed and in progress,", April 1953 (Box-folder 27: 29)
  - "Unpublished research on Korea - completed and in progress,", April 1953 (Box-folder 27: 30)
  - "Unpublished research on the Near East - completed and in progress,", April 1953 (Box-folder 27: 31)
  - "Unpublished research on Southeast Asia - completed and in progress,", April 1953 (Box-folder 27: 32)
  - "Unpublished research on U.S.S.R. - completed and in progress,", April 1953 (Box-folder 27: 33)
  - "Unpublished research on Western Europe - completed and in progress,", April 1953 (Box-folder 27: 34)
  - Fourne: "Weight estimation for airplanes,", January 1947 (Box-folder 27: 35)
- Box 28
  - Schile: "Arrangement of radiators for rear engine installations,", 15 February 1945 (Box-folder 28: 1)
  - Kaufmann: "Directives for designing and testing of pressure cabins for high altitude aircraft,", November 22 1941 (Box-folder 28: 2)
  - Meissinger: "Diving of high-speed fighter airplane,", October 1944 (Box-folder 28: 3)
  - Schnetzer: "Further development of DB 603 engine with gas ejector pump,", October 1940 (Box-folder 28: 4)
  - Wichmann: "General survey of synthetic materials, their manufacture, processing and industrial use,", March 1943 (Box-folder 28: 5)
  - Schulze: "Influence of the heating time on the size of grain in magnesium-alloys,", August 1938 (Box-folder 28: 6)
  - Lemme: "Investigation of aileron effectiveness of a sweptback wing and a blunted sweptback back wing,", July 1944 (Box-folder 28: 7)
  - Linke: "Light metal systems for liquid coolants,", May 1944 (Box-folder 28: 8)
  - "Magnesium and its alloys,", October 1941 (Box-folder 28: 9)
  - Welz: "Measurements of aileron effectiveness of a profile of 15% maximum thickess and 50% thickness location with small trailing edge angle,", July 1944 (Box-folder 28: 10)
  - Guerard: "Method for considering wing stiffness in evaluating gliders,", 20 December 1939 (Box-folder 28: 11)
  - Ludwig: "Optimum coefficients in a characterstic aerodynamic stability equation,", May 1941 (Box-folder 28: 12)
  - Kaiser: "Protective screens for air inlets in turbojet engines,", February 1945 (Box-folder 28: 13)
  - Mueller: "Specification for bonding of airplane parts,", March 1944 (Box-folder 28: 14)
  - "Specifications on aircraft materials,", October 1942 (Box-folder 28: 15)
  - "Theoretical fundamentals of navigation,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 28: 16)
  - Kühnrich: "Working on magnesium alloys,", 23 June 1941 (Box-folder 28: 17)
- Box 29
  - Farben & Bitterfield: "Bestimmung der Dauerstandsfestigkeit [sigma]1/300 bei 80[degrees], 100[degrees], 120[degrees], 150[degrees] an verschiedenen Anlieferungen und Abmessungen,", 21 May 1940 (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Mann: "Comparison tests of three magnesium-aluminum alloys,", November 1934 (Box-folder 29: 2)
  - Brenner: "Corrosion tests on aluminum-magnesium (Elektron) sheets under load,", January 1933 (Box-folder 29: 3)
  - Scheidt: "Determination of most favorable salt bath annealing temperatures for various alloys of the Dural type,", March 1935 (Box-folder 29: 4)
  - Boelkow: "Drag at high speeds,", January 1942 (Box-folder 29: 5)
  - Lucht: "E-395 superspeed bomber with 4 HES 109011A engines,", February 1944 (Box-folder 29: 6)
  - Fahrenhorst: "Encrystallization of magnesium in the cast state,", February 1942 (Box-folder 29: 7)
  - Froessel: "Experimental investigation of the compressible flow on and near a curved wall; I: free flow,", May 1944 (Box-folder 29: 8)
  - Thiergarten & Cosming: "First test runs of the HeS 011 turbojet engine,", January 1943 (Box-folder 29: 9)
  - Bungardt: "Inspection of a new magnesium alloy,", 13 July 1938 (Box-folder 29: 10)
  - Bollenrath, Cornelius, & Bungardt: "Investigation heat-resisting materials for exhaust gas turbine blades mechanical and physical properties (Part 1 of 4 Parts),", October 1937 (Box-folder 29: 11)
  - Haehnel & Reinmiedl: "Jamming of ground observation equipment by synchronising their impulses with transmitting impulses,", 9 April 1945 (Box-folder 29: 12)
  - Sahliger: "Measurements on a 35 degree sweptback wing at the Chalais Neudon wind tunnel,", June 1944 (Box-folder 29: 13)
  - Dirksen: "Nozzles of heat-resisting materials,", February 1945 (Box-folder 29: 14)
  - Betreff: "Outline for development of high-speed jet-propelled aircraft,", October 1944 (Box-folder 29: 15)
  - Fahrenhorst: "Report on 2 chill-cast ingots of magnesium alloys,", October 1943 (Box-folder 29: 16)
  - Laemmchen: "Report on the fighter and bomber control radar Egen,", 18 November 1944 (Box-folder 29: 17)
  - Angel: "Suggestion for a blind landing procedure with radar devices,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 29: 18)
  - Sauer & Heinz: "Two-dimensional supersonic flow in a converging duct,", August 1944 (Box-folder 29: 19)
  - Steinheil & Soehne: "Various aircraft gunsights,", 5 February 1941 (Box-folder 29: 20)
- Box 30
  - Smidt: "Tests on magnesium alloys consisting of the German aircraft materials 3505.0 and 3507.9,", April 1942 (Box-folder 30: 1)
  - "Specifications on aircraft materials,", October 1942 (Box-folder 30: 2)
  - "Six component measurements on a rectangular wing with variously formed tips,", 2 July 1943 (Box-folder 30: 3)
  - Kuechermann: "Basic principles of a jet wing,", July 1944 (Box-folder 30: 4)
  - Keul & Wuppermann: "Apparatus for the remote recording of measurements,", July 1943 (Box-folder 30: 5)
  - Lehnert: "Wind tunnel tests at 4.3 mach numbers" (Part 8 of 12 parts), October 1941 (Box-folder 30: 6)
  - Trentini: "Absorption of radar echo pulses,", November 1943 (Box-folder 30: 7)
  - Roth: "The production of magnesium ingots by different casting methods,", February 1942 (Box-folder 30: 8)
- Box 31
  - Wysocki: "3-component tests on aircraft snow-runners,", 15 March 1941 (Box-folder 31: 1)
  - Hoerner: "The aerodynamics of three dimensional bodies,", August 1944 (Box-folder 31: 2)
  - Schmitz: "Course of motion, impact forces and spring strokes in the landing of a nose-wheel airplane", 1943 (Box-folder 31: 3)
  - Hermann: "Density measurements with x-rays in a supersonic wind tunnel stream,", 11 January 1944 (Box-folder 31: 4)
  - Hoerner: "The determination of parasitic wing tip drag,", 1943 (Box-folder 31: 5)
  - Zeiler: "Experiences with various slat-kinematics of the ME 210,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 31: 6)
  - Walz: "Experiments with removal of friction layer by suction on a wing profile NACA 23015 with different positions of the suction slots along the cord,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 31: 7)
  - Voigt, Walter & Heger: "Flutter experiments on the influence of aerodynamic balance of a path-controlled auxiliary control surface,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 31: 8)
  - Messerschmitt: "General summary of turbo-jet & propeller turbo jet-engines,", 15 November 1944 (Box-folder 31: 9)
  - Keil: "The high-speed spark camera,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 31: 10)
  - Ernsthausen: "The influence of aerodynamic properties upon the field of sound and radiation output of an air screw,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 31: 11)
  - Jordan & Kraus: "Infra-red radiation from the boundary layer of missile "Wasserfall" in motion,", 20 September 1943 (Box-folder 31: 12)
  - Vettin: "On the integration of non-linear differential equations,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 31: 13)
  - Neuber: "On the stability of longitudinally connected bars,", 1941 (Box-folder 31: 14)
  - Doetsch: "On velocities attainable in the next few years,", June 1945 (Box-folder 31: 15)
  - Schaefer: "Outflow of a jet of compressed air into moving air,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 31: 16)
  - Berthold: "Research on the design of a continuous-operation wind tunnel for subsonic and supersonic velocities with maximum possible efficiency,", 6 May 1941 (Box-folder 31: 17)
  - Multhopp: "Slide rule for the determination of the true flight speed,", 11 November 1942 (Box-folder 31: 18)
  - Borkmann & Dietze: "Tables for airforces theory of the harmonically vibrating wing,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 31: 19)
  - Scheubel: "The tail-less airplane in comparison to conventional types,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 31: 20)
  - Lommel: "Theoretical and experimental investigations of diffraction phenomena at a circular aperture and obstacle,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 31: 21)
  - Dr. F. Porsche company: "Three turbine design curves,", November 1944 (Box-folder 31: 22)
- Box 32
  - Scholkemeier: "6-component tests on 3 swept wings with and without fuselage,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 32: 1)
  - Office of Naval Intelligence: "The Aerialdynamic-Ballistic Research Institute WVA Kochel in the Service of Aerialnautical Research,", 2 September 1941 (Box-folder 32: 2)
  - Schlinger: "Bismuth Sulfide Thermo-elements,", circa 1941 (Box-folder 32: 3)
  - Schwarz, "Contribution to the Stationary Airfoil Theory,", 10 November 1939 (Box-folder 32: 4)
  - Grunewald & Kraus: "Experimental study of shock formation on cones at supersonic speed,", 13 April 1944 (Box-folder 32: 5)
  - Rott: "The field of a fast moving sound source,", 15 January 1945 (Box-folder 32: 6)
  - Schubert: "The flow over an infinite wedge and around an infinite cone at α=∞,", 11 May 1943 (Box-folder 32: 7)
  - Pfenninger: "Investigations on friction decrease of airfoils, especially by means of boundary layer bleeding by suction,", 22 March 1951 (Box-folder 32: 8)
  - Schade: "Numerical solution of the Possio integral equation of the oscillating wing in steady sobsonic flow,", 27 November 1944 (Box-folder 32: 9)
  - Aeronautical Engine Laboratory: "Preliminary Technical Data on the Daimler-Benz 109-021 A-O Propeller Turbo-Jet-Engine,", 1 March 1945 (Box-folder 32: 10)
  - Schmidt: "The Schmidt Tube,", 15 June 1944 (Box-folder 32: 11)
  - Fyertag: "Subsonic and supersonic wind tunnel measurements on the stabilization of the long range rocket Rh Z M 4,", 4 January 1946 (Box-folder 32: 12)
  - Vueller and Knobloch: "Test results on aerial missiles in the sonic range of speed,", 23 November 1944 (Box-folder 32: 13)
  - Untitled figures, undated (Box-folder 32: 14)
- Box 33
  - Liess: "3-component tests on the Rheinmetal devices R 100 M2 and R 100 M3 in the supersonic wind tunnel,", 3 April 1946 (Box-folder 33: 1)
  - Liess & Weber: "3-component tests on a surface-stablized projectile form R 100 MS in the supersonic wind tunnel,", 9 April 1946 (Box-folder 33: 2)
  - Strassl: "3-component tests on short cylinders at supersonic velocities,", 3 April 1946 (Box-folder 33: 3)
  - Weber & Höckner: "3-component tests on the device "Kurt" in the supersonic wind tunnel,", 3 April 1946 (Box-folder 33: 4)
  - Weber: "3-component tests on several drop-grenades in the wind tunnel at supersonic velocities,", 9 April 1946 (Box-folder 33: 5)
  - Weber: "3-component tests on the projectile form R 100 BS in the supersonic wind tunnel,", 10 April 1946 (Box-folder 33: 6)
  - Pinsker: "The aerodynamic coefficients of free lateral motion,", November 1946 (Box-folder 33: 7)
  - Busemann: "Aerodynamic lift at supersonic speeds,", circa 1935 (Box-folder 33: 8)
  - Albring: "Basic theories for determining angles of attack on bodies of revolution by pressure measurements,", 18 February 1946 (Box-folder 33: 9)
  - W. Mangler: "Boundary layers on bodies of revolution in symmetrical flow,", 26 June 1946 (Box-folder 33: 10)
  - Küchemann and Weber: "Concerning the flow over the covering of annular shapes,", November 1946 (Box-folder 33: 11)
  - Ludwieg: " Determination of performance factors of muzzle-brakes,", 10 April 1946 (Box-folder 33: 12)
  - Egglink: "Flow structure and pressure recovery in supersonic tunnels,", undated (Box-folder 33: 13)
  - Holst: "The propelling wing,", 6 February 1947 (Box-folder 33: 14)
  - Ludwieg: "Subsonic and supersonic wind tunnel measurements on the stabilization of a long distance rocket,", 1 April 1946 (Box-folder 33: 15)
  - O. Pabst: "Systematic burner experiments with illuminating gas,", 6 January 1942 (Box-folder 33: 16)
  - Brennecke & Keydell: "Tests on a roll angle-steady flight body,", 29 March 1945 (Box-folder 33: 17)
  - Brennecke & Keydell: "Tests on a roll angle-steady flight body,", 4 January 1946 (Box-folder 33: 18)
  - Brennecke & Keydell: "Tests on a roll angle-steady flight body,", undated (Box-folder 33: 19)
  - Prandtl: "Theory of the airplane wing in compressible media,", 12 October 1936 (Box-folder 33: 20)
  - Liess: "Wind tunnel tests on a bomb model SE 1000 at supersonic speeds,", 4 March 1946 (Box-folder 33: 21)
  - Feyertag: "Wind tunnel tests on models of a 5.5cm M-projectile at supersonic velocities,", 4 March 1946 (Box-folder 33: 22)
  - Holbig & Weber: "Wind tunnel tests on a model of a 7.5cm grenade HL 43,", 10 April 1946 (Box-folder 33: 23)
  - Feyertag: "Wind tunnel tests on a model of an SE 1000 bomb at subsonic speeds,", 3 April 1946 (Box-folder 33: 24)
- Box 34
  - Pinkser: "The aerodynamic coefficients of free lateral motion, 1st partial report,", undated (Box-folder 34: 1)
  - Pinkser: "The aerodynamic coefficients of free lateral motion, 2nd partial report,", undated (Box-folder 34: 2)
  - Sack: "Analysis of airflow of the exhaust pipe,", 28 March 1945 (Box-folder 34: 3)
  - Research Institute for Aircraft Radio: "Arrangement for generating short, high-frequency pulses,", 8 November 1941 (Box-folder 34: 4)
  - Aviation overhead projector transparencies, undated (Box-folder 34: 5)
  - Dessauer: "Elimination of electrostatic self-charging of aircraft,", February 1944 (Box-folder 34: 6)
  - Hahn: "Evaluation of turbo-pump Br 3-18,", June 1940 (Box-folder 34: 7)
  - BMW: "Installation manual for BMW 003 R turbojet with rocket booster,", November 1943 (Box-folder 34: 8)
  - Rüster: "Introduction into tolerances with examples for airplane design" with translation, 1942 (Box-folder 34: 9-10)
  - Schubert: "Leistungeschanbilder für den Flugseugentwurf,", 1 January 1945 (Box-folder 34: 11)
  - List of German aviation abbreviations, undated (Box-folder 34: 12)
  - Zech: "Local changes of air resistance caused, for example, by weather conditions, and the effect produced on the fire range,", 19 March 1947 (Box-folder 34: 13)
  - Gesellschaft: "New investigations on airplane noises,", 22 March 1951 (Box-folder 34: 14)
  - Sinkmann: "Performance of Me 410 (two engine fighter-bomber) with auxiliary turbojet units,", September 1943 (Box-folder 34: 15)
  - Pabst: "The performance quantities of Lorin propulsion units characterized by complete stoppage of air,", 8 February 1946 (Box-folder 34: 16)
  - Krueger: "Range measurement and its effect on the lead angle,", August 1942 (Box-folder 34: 17)
  - Schrenk: "Research on boundary layer control at the Gottingen Institute of Aerodynamics,", 14 January 1946 (Box-folder 34: 18)
  - Ringleb: "Some aerodynamic relations for an airfoil in oblique flow,", 21 October 1941 (Box-folder 34: 19)
  - Schmid: "Tentative description of construction of flying wing 229,", 21 February 1946 (Box-folder 34: 20)
- Box 35
  - Mathias: "Aerodynamics of NACA-FW (FOCKE-WUIF) airfoils,", 13 March 1942 (Box-folder 35: 1)
  - Lindemann: "Comparison of results on various aircraft models from the DVL high speed wind tunnel,", July 1946 (Box-folder 35: 2)
  - Pabst: "The design of Lorin-propulsion,", February 1944 (Box-folder 35: 3)
  - Kendler: "Discussion of testing the newly developed electronically heated windows,", 5 August 1941 (Box-folder 35: 4)
  - Göthert: "Influence of individual roughness features on the drag of wing profiles,", July 1946 (Box-folder 35: 5)
  - Betz: "The keeping laminar of the boundary layer at high Reynolds numbers,", 15 March 1946 (Box-folder 35: 6)
  - J. Pretsch: "Limits of boundary layer control,", 15 February 1946 (Box-folder 35: 7)
  - Lindemann: "Measurements of longitudal stability at high mach numbers,", July 1946 (Box-folder 35: 8)
  - Solf: "On the dynamic lateral stability of a towed airplane,", undated (Box-folder 35: 9)
  - Stratmann & Müller: "Problems concerning steel spars for the FW300 transport,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 35: 10)
  - Böthert: "Profile tests in the high speed wind tunnel of the DVL,", April 1946 (Box-folder 35: 11)
  - Geduldig & Schindler: "Project development of the Me 210 ice protection,", undated (Box-folder 35: 12-14)
  - Hansen: "Thermodynamic problems of windshields,", undated (Box-folder 35: 15)
  - Krueger: "Wind tunnel tests on a reworked Mustang profile with nose flap,", undated (Box-folder 35: 16)
  - Unidentified German charts, undated (Box-folder 35: 17)
- Box 36
  - Volak: "Development of windshields protected against the formation of ice,", undated (Box-folder 36: 1)
  - Schiller: "Experimental determination of the damping coefficient of flat plates vibrating in subsonic flow,", undated (Box-folder 36: 2)
  - Walz: " Experiments with removal of friction layer by suction on a wing profile NACA 23015 with different positions of the suction slots along the card,", undated (Box-folder 36: 3)
  - H. Kurzweg: "Fundamental aerodynamic investigations for the development of Peenemünde fin-stabalized projectiles,", 27 October 1942 (Box-folder 36: 4)
  - Erdmann: "Hinge-moment tests on spin rudders of A4 in the supersonic and compressible regimes,", 5 March 1942 (Box-folder 36: 5)
  - ISA system of fits photonegatives, 1923-1936 (Box-folder 36: 6-7)
  - Wagner: "Investigation of the air flow requirements of wing model Ar232 for boundary layer control by means of jet pumps,", March 1943 (Box-folder 36: 8)
  - Ramm: "Measurements of thermodynamic quantities in supersonic flows,", 6 December 1941 (Box-folder 36: 9)
  - Schubert: "Performance charts for airplane designing,", January 1945 (Box-folder 36: 10)
  - Sieckmann: "Performance of fighter aircraft with otto or turbojet engine,", undated (Box-folder 36: 11)
  - Muttray: "The problem of pressurized cabins,", May 1942 (Box-folder 36: 12)
  - Novotny: "Rectangular wing with fixed slat and fairing over slot,", February 1944 (Box-folder 36: 13)
  - Lehnert: "Rolling moment measurements on a model A4V1P, equipped with aerodynamic roll controls,", 7 January 1942 (Box-folder 36: 14)
  - Herrman & Lehnert: "Study of the improvement of the aerodynamic stability of the 6.7cm rocket device (P2.4) of the firm WASAG by moving the center of gravity forward and changing the tail assembly,", 25 June 1942 (Box-folder 36: 15)
  - Herrman & Lehnert: "Three-component measurements on an aerodynamically improved form of the anti-aircraft rocket C-2,", 14 July 1943 (Box-folder 36: 16)
  - Raffel: "Three-component measurements on the model of the Peenemünde arrow shell PPG/F/N/3400/0.5N/1/A,", 13 April 1943 (Box-folder 36: 17)
  - Lehnert: "Three component measurements on a model of the Peenemünde arrow shell PPG 180K/5 in the supersonic wind tunnel of the Peenemünde Army Establishment,", 29 June 1942 (Box-folder 36: 18)
  - Wegener: "Wind tunnel tests to find the influence of speed and center of gravity on the controllability of C2/E2 of the project 'Wasserfall',", 1943-1944 (Box-folder 36: 19)
  - Gerecke: "Wind tunnel tests on a model of the rocket-projectile 'Rheintochter',", 29 March 1946 (Box-folder 36: 20)
- Box 37
  - Gropler: "Aerodynamic and structural design considerations for wings with high degree of sweepback,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 37: 1)
  - Marquard: "Approximative calculation of the spring forces acting between undercarriage and fuselage in landing,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 37: 2)
  - Preussler: "The calibration of cold-drawn sections,", 10 November 1949 (Box-folder 37: 3)
  - Krüger: "Collection and comparison of various designs and means,", 1944 (Box-folder 37: 4)
  - Heinrich: "Drop test with chute-stabalized bombs BM1000, SC 1000, SD 500, SC500,", 18 November 1943 (Box-folder 37: 5)